pokerpromagazine.com 2015-03-17

# Poker Policy-Poker Pro magazine | Poker Pro Magazine

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of Poker Pro Media Worldwide’s sites, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement (the”Statement”) discloses the privacy practices for Poker Pro Media Worldwide sites (the “Website”) – what information we gather, how we use it and how to correct or change it. This Statement only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those to which the Web site links and third party sites providing services to Poker Pro Media Worldwide sites) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control.

**General Privacy Information**

The Website contains links to partners, advertisers and third party Internet sites and services who may collect data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, e-commerce, etc. They each have separate, privacy and data collection practices, and the Website has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Further, Poker Pro Media Worldwide is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**Registration**

Anyone who participates in interactive activities (subscriptions, opinion posting, surveys and polls, contests, product purchase, etc.) on the Website may be asked to register for a free guest ID and password or to complete subscription registration for a member ID and password. We use customer contact information from this registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary for customer service reasons. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings. Unique identifier such as ID and passwords, are collected to verify the user’s identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your username(s), password(s), and your account(s), as well as all activities that occur under your account(s).

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. The Website collects personal information from visitors during account registration, through sign-ups for newsletter and magazine subscriptions, via survey and contests participation, and other marketing campaigns.

Poker Pro Media Worldwide uses your data to administer your subscription, provide information of interest to you, and to communicate with you. Your data is stored in the United States.

Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address, birth date, and credit card information. In addition, we may collect demographic information, details about your use of the Website and other data that you may provide. We may combine demographic information with personal information to tailor our offerings or the Website to your preferences or interests.

**Children**

When creating an account, we require the new member to certify that he or she is 18 years old or over by checking the appropriate box. If a child under age 18 attempts to register on our sites, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian create a family account instead.

**Changing or Updating Your Information**

You can correct or update your account information at any time by contacting Poker Pro Media Worldwide through the methods below. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as needed. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our terms of use, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Website.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is extremely important to us. We follow widely accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number numbers) on our registration or other forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use all possible means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that certain sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you’ve visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. This random number lets us keep track of “how many” times customers are doing specific things, such as visiting the Website, without really knowing who those customers are. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your member ID. Additionally, after you’ve entered your member ID and password during a session on our service, we save that information so you don’t have to reenter it repeatedly during that session.

The Website cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for our sites. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information available on the Website).

**Surveys and Polls**

Our online surveys and polls may ask visitors for their e-mail address and demographic information. Demographic and profile data is also collected at the Website. We use this data to tailor the visitor experience at our site.  This information is shared with advertisers only on an aggregate basis. We may use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from Poker Pro Media Worldwide or some of our partners. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings.

**Contests**

We may run contests on the Website in which we ask visitors for our site IDs and passwords. We use contact data from our contests to send users information about upcoming contests and promotional offers. On occasion we will email participants promotional information from some of our partners. The participant’s contact information is also used when necessary for winner notification and prize delivery confirmation. There may be cases in which a third party sponsor will host the contest and collect user information. In those cases, we urge users to review the privacy statement of the third party site. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

The Website reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy without notice. In the event of a change of this policy, procedures will be developed for users to opt-out or otherwise prohibit any future use of their individually identifiable information that is not currently covered under this policy. Policy changes will be posted on this page.

**Compliance with Legal Process**

We may disclose your personal information as required by law or if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our sites; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

**Contacting Our Site**

Questions regarding this Statement and Website should be e-mailed to [accounts@pokerpromedia.com](mailto:accounts@pokerpromedia.com) or mailed to Poker Pro Media Worldwide, P. O. Box 7194, Delray Beach, FL 33482.
